The Board's coming given the direction of their social support. Father, we love you and I want to honor
you with the community that we have. So, hope was to do well and I'd like us
that's why it is a more significant amount than normal three combined. We've had
lot of activity obviously going on through April May, in June reviewing comments
That were filed with FERC by GRDA and lots
Of Comments we have been receiving several reports from the report
that have been filed and were requested by FERC. We met with our hydrologists,
which are attorneys in hydrologist than we've met
And I'm discussing protection mitigation enhancement measures
So it's just being a lot of activity going on but this particular invoice was well within the budget
amount for fiscal year
And we'll leave a remaining balance of 244,000 and 21 dollars in for cents
For the fiscal year 2223. So these invoices will come out
Of last years's fiscal budget
Second
Hi
Thank
hi
Hey
The award-lease purchase agreement
Do bank or grant rate
For our P23-33 purchase of one
Brooks, BRS
UP
Brooks
Brothers trailer
And give related signing
Compagament authority
To the city manager is his deputy
He's actually an underground fireholder
The invoice I all
And the rates came down at 775%
Down to 4.3 per cent
Bank of brand by 1599290
So Brian we get in trailer with it?
Yeah
In all that
We have a pro
Fight over
His Berks Brothers trailers
Is Adam, is That A Brand or
Does that like
Trailer
The normally carry pull along
To do
Do you need
Be right on this and say
What he actually
He's
Well I think
It
cryptic because it's a lot of numbers. The Vimal match though so we have something
You know I'll be in number that matches what? We haven't on our documentation
Yeah, we have a number showing here and you know how to describe or entitled these things
We just need the make sure once that's what came out I'll take motion.
The war bid C 23 this is Number 9
The war bid C 23 dash 35 contract for distribution line relocation 520 road to BBC electric services incorporated
In the middle of 170,800 approved contract contingent upon this mission required documents and a pretty city manager has heard his design need
To sign notice proceed
We send background to the police on chase and how they will all spend plans for it is bid out of process
You said this totally reimbursable. Is that you have take a low as big? On something like
The best idea, if there are other ways
I think we'll push too approve
Second
Thank you
Ten another new business
Which is the reason to post it since opposeding this agenda 11 staff reports community or trustee community announcements Kevin wants them else
Well happy birthday Jennifer. It's your birthday today
You're welcome
I don't think he had a birthday turn
That would be a violation of me
Thank you, Valle
I feel like i'm in jail
He said he's a good Stanford birthday. That's it for you
This is your 13 this mean what we continue
Counts favors if re-convenient staff room purpose of executive session at the end
The MIPFA meet